[{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678864126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":9657,"timeElapsed":56652},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678869163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5036,"timeElapsed":61689},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678874825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5661,"timeElapsed":67351},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678882969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":8143,"timeElapsed":75495},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678886788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3818,"timeElapsed":79314},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678897039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":10250,"timeElapsed":89565},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678900184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3144,"timeElapsed":92710},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678904607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4422,"timeElapsed":97133},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678907044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2436,"timeElapsed":99570},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678923355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":15322,"timeElapsed":115881},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678926960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3604,"timeElapsed":119486},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678929028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2067,"timeElapsed":121554},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678933766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4737,"timeElapsed":126292},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678935439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1672,"timeElapsed":127965},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678938010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2570,"timeElapsed":130536},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678939918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1907,"timeElapsed":132444},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678943483,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3565,"timeElapsed":136009},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678945236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1752,"timeElapsed":137762},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678953968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":7817,"timeElapsed":146494},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678955695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1726,"timeElapsed":148221},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678958906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3210,"timeElapsed":151432},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678963060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4154,"timeElapsed":155586},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678965491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2430,"timeElapsed":158017},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678967404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1912,"timeElapsed":159930},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678968917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1512,"timeElapsed":161443},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678970954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2036,"timeElapsed":163480},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678972392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1437,"timeElapsed":164918},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678978160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4319,"timeElapsed":170686},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678980116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1955,"timeElapsed":172642},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678982513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2397,"timeElapsed":175039},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678988011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5497,"timeElapsed":180537},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678989799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1787,"timeElapsed":182325},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678991522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1722,"timeElapsed":184048},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678992640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1117,"timeElapsed":185166},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678995132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2491,"timeElapsed":187658},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678997379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2246,"timeElapsed":189905},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679004803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":6559,"timeElapsed":197329},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679007275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2471,"timeElapsed":199801},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679009133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1857,"timeElapsed":201659},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679013611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4477,"timeElapsed":206137},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679014370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":759,"timeElapsed":206896},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679016447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2076,"timeElapsed":208973},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679017331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":883,"timeElapsed":209857},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679019787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2455,"timeElapsed":212313},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679021994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2206,"timeElapsed":214520},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679029728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6829,"timeElapsed":222254},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679032993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3264,"timeElapsed":225519},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679038999,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6005,"timeElapsed":231525},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679042345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3345,"timeElapsed":234871},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679047773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5427,"timeElapsed":240299},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679049880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":2106,"timeElapsed":242406},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679053530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3649,"timeElapsed":246056},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679054708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1177,"timeElapsed":247234},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679057590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2881,"timeElapsed":250116},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679059991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2400,"timeElapsed":252517},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679067821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6930,"timeElapsed":260347},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679069988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2166,"timeElapsed":262514},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679075980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5991,"timeElapsed":268506},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679081033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":5052,"timeElapsed":273559},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679082761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1727,"timeElapsed":275287},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1566,"timeElapsed":276854},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679088378,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4049,"timeElapsed":280904},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2261,"timeElapsed":283166},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3649,"timeElapsed":286816},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679096802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2512,"timeElapsed":289328},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679108966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":11074,"timeElapsed":301492},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679112696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3729,"timeElapsed":305222},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4068,"timeElapsed":309291},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679118733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1967,"timeElapsed":311259},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679119671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":937,"timeElapsed":312197},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679124540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4868,"timeElapsed":317066},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679126073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1532,"timeElapsed":318599},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679130342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4268,"timeElapsed":322868},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679134057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3714,"timeElapsed":326583},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679141212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6071,"timeElapsed":333738},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679144083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2870,"timeElapsed":336609},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679148712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4628,"timeElapsed":341238},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679154345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5632,"timeElapsed":346871},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679155574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1228,"timeElapsed":348100},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679158221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2646,"timeElapsed":350747},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679160048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1826,"timeElapsed":352574},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679162340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2291,"timeElapsed":354866},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679163658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1317,"timeElapsed":356184},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":5877,"timeElapsed":363011},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679172103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1617,"timeElapsed":364629},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3015,"timeElapsed":367645},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2096,"timeElapsed":369742},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679178694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1477,"timeElapsed":371220},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679183637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4942,"timeElapsed":376163},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679184826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1188,"timeElapsed":377352},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679189145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4319,"timeElapsed":381671},{"subjectID":"6vcm23zh3a","prolificID":"5e164e81502213c397f0cf39","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b437cecf6b43e15a501","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679190458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1312,"timeElapsed":382984}]